

OBJECTIVE

With a willingness to learn, grow and sustain in areas outside my expertise, I look forward to explore along with being a hard worker to achieve my goals. A zeal to excel in the challenges that are offered and perform to the best of my abilities.

CONTACT

PHONE: 9804019155

EMAIL:

pramanik.85849@gmail.com

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ankit-pramanik-179765181/

GITHUB:

https://github.com/ankit98040

HOBBIES

Learning New Technologies Writing stories Travelling Photography

PERSONAL DETAILS:

DATE OF BIRTH: 06/ JANUARY/ 1999 ADDRESS: BARRACKPORE, KOLKATA

ANKIT PRAMANIK

EDUCATION

RCC Institute of Information Technology

2017 - 2021

Specialization: Information Technology

CGPA: 7.45 (Upto 5th sem)

WORK EXPERIENCE

National Institute of Industrial Training: Technical Consultant

JANUARY 2020 - JULY 2020

At NiiT I was the Technical Instructor in the field of Data Science And Machine Learning along with working in the field of Data Analytics and Data Visualization.

Techsim+: Backend Developer Internship

May 2020 - June 2020

To create and maintain the complete backend using Django.

TAKENMIND.COM PVT LTD: DATA ANALYTICS & VISUALIZATION INTERN

JANUARY 2020 - FEBRUARY 2020

The Takenmind Internship primarily focused on the work of data analytics and data visualization.

SKILL SET

Frontend: React.js

Backend: Node.js, Django **Database**: Mongo DB, MySql

Cloud: AWS, GCP

OS: Windows, Linux, Mac os, RHEL

Others: Docker, GIT etc

PROJECTS

- 1. Login System (Node.js, Mongo Db)
- 2. Chatting Web Server (Node.js, Socket.io)
- 3. Integration of Django with Image Processing
- 4. E-Commerce Web-App using React.js